https://missouri.edu/privacy/

Skip to navigation
Skip to content
Mizzou to temporarily shift to remote learning after Thanksgiving. See Show Me Renewal Updates. More info at Missouri Dept. of Health & Senior Services and the CDC.
Find Info For...
Students
Faculty & Staff
Families
Alumni
Mizzou A-Z
MU Alert
Directory
News
Map
Find info for...
Students
Faculty & Staff
Families
Alumni
University of Missouri Privacy Policy
Home
University of Missouri Privacy Policy
The University of Missouri is committed to protecting your privacy.  This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this website. Please read this privacy policy before using the website or submitting any personal information. By using the website, you are accepting the practices described in this policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the website to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. If you follow a link on this site to another website, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Non-Personal Information
The University of Missouri collects non-personal information about your Internet connection on its websites, including but not limited to:
the Internet Protocol (IP) and the name of the Internet domain you used to access the Internet
the IP address or URL of the web site from which you directly linked to this website
the date and time you accessed this website
the pages you visited on this website
the browser and operating system you used to access this website
the search terms used on our search engines
The University of Missouri uses this non-personal information to help manage the website and improve service.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The University of Missouri uses Google Analytics to gather statistics about web site traffic.  Cookies or tracking pixels are used for various purposes within web sites to gather information and facilitate navigation. The University of Missouri web sites use cookies or tracking pixels for re-marketing.  For more information, read Google Analytic’s privacy policy.
Personally Identifiable Information
There are various locations on the University of Missouri websites where you may submit registration information. We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request.Our online forms should indicate the information that is required and the information that is optional - you do not have to complete any “optional” fields on a form. However, to be able to submit an online form, you must supply the required information. Providing personal information on-line will always be your choice. The personal information that you supply will not be sold to others.
If you choose to connect to our website through a social network such as Facebook, we may automatically collect your profile information. These things allow us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you and to measure traffic on the website. Learn more about Facebook’s privacy policy here.
E-mail
If you send the University of Missouri an e-mail, the message will usually contain your return address. If you include personal information in your e-mail, we may use that information in responding to your request. E-mail is not necessarily secure or confidential. Send only the information that is necessary for us to answer your question or process your request.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place.
Commitment to Data Security
The University of Missouri takes reasonable steps to ensure that your information is protected. Only authorized employees, agents, and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this website allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us at the following email address: digitalservice@missouri.edu
The University of Missouri provides information on GDPR requirements and university processes at https://www.umsystem.edu/ums/is/infosec/gdpr. This privacy policy complies with Missouri statutes, the California Consumer Privacy Act and United States Federal regulations. We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
